<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aditya Kushwaha</title>
    <description>Mobile &amp; Product Developer. Former Lead Android Engineer at Zomato</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 20:04:05 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 20:04:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v9</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This version saw a major shift in how we handled our network and data. The underlying layers - network, transport and data were revisited for the first time since 2012, benchmarked against the industry standards and overhauled. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We moved from parsing data using archaic XML parsers to the new age GSON parsers, changed our HTTP client to OkHttp3 for an array of improvements.
You can read more about this change on &lt;a href=&quot;https://engineering.zomato.com/rewriting-the-network-connection-layer-in-our-android-apps-11771c71012#.q88rc7v0k&quot;&gt;Zomato’s Engineering blog. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version also included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bottom Navigation on the Home page&lt;/b&gt; - We completely redessigned the Home Page to have mutiple fragments and placed a navigational tab at the bottom. These new tabs led to easier navigational UX.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Introduced &lt;b&gt;Table Reservations through the app&lt;/b&gt; -  We started a new vertical of operations to get into online table reservations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Integrated our inhouse &lt;b&gt;Data Analysing Engine (Jumbo!)&lt;/b&gt; deep into the app - Moving past GA (Google Analytics), we integrated our inhouse data tool to give insights into user lifecycle &amp;amp; behavior, trends and feature usage. Events and screens were logged and batched light-weight API calls made near real-time monitoring possible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Google App Indexing&lt;/b&gt; - Read about App Indexing on the official &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/training/app-indexing/index.html&quot;&gt;Android Developer’s&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requesting Permissions at Runtime&lt;/b&gt; - Reworkd all the permissions in the app and started to ask for permission at run time instead of install time. Read more about them on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/training/permissions/requesting.html&quot;&gt; Android Developer’s&lt;/a&gt; page.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Home Page with a Bottom Navigation Bar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/v9/v9_home.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Runtime permissions&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/v9/v9_permissions.jpg&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;User page with detailed ‘Dineline’&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/v9/v9_user_dineline.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v9</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v9</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v8</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our super fast development cycles and the convoluted nature of our product gave rise to the ideology of development kits. We thought of the entire product as a complex organism and then broke things down to atoms and molecules - and thus multiple development kits were born - we had an UI Kit, Network Kit, Online Ordering Kit, Image Handling kit…you get the idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This version saw a major cleanup of our code into functional and robust libraries and development kits - such was the ease of usage of the kits that we even tied up with a Snapdeal, Helpchat and the likes by providing them with our Online Ordering kit. Read more about this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.financialexpress.com/industry/zomato-gets-personal-helpchat/315431/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.financialexpress.com/industry/snapdeal-launches-flights-food-bus-tickets-services-expands-into-100-billion-market/306284/&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version also included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete backward combatibility with &lt;b&gt;Marshmallow&lt;/b&gt; - With the release of Android 6.0 major code changes were needed to make sure every aspect of the app worked fine.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The &lt;b&gt;app size came under 10 Mb&lt;/b&gt; for the first time in two years!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Image Filters!&lt;/b&gt; - &lt;em&gt;watch this space Instagram! ahem!&lt;/em&gt; And guess what, we open sourced it - Read more about it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://engineering.zomato.com/our-first-open-source-contribution-stunning-photo-filters-for-your-android-apps-725eaffd0080&quot;&gt; Zomato’s Engineering blog&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Zomato/AndroidPhotoFilters&quot;&gt;fork it on GitHub!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Invited by Google to be one of world’s first 20 products to integrate &lt;b&gt;Google Now cards.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Moved from multiple tabs on Home to a single tab app with importance to the &lt;b&gt;Hamburger menu&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Integration with Uber.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Home Page with the Hamburger menu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v8/home.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo Upload Flow with the new Image Filters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v8/photo_upload.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Search with Map view and List view&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v8/search.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v8</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v8</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v7</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In the biggest ever move for us, we acquired UrbanSpoon! Our combined userbase grew four times and the number of cities of operation went from 250 to 10,000! 
With time, we transitioned our users, scaled our systems and evolved to play with loads of data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this huge transition - life as we knew it had changed - Along with our logo, size of our userbase and areas of operation, multiple legacy algorithms and systems started to fail by the sheer scale of our data. We had to rework a lot of our logic to cater to this monumental scale of sessions on the app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version also included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Certificate Pinning using Deffie Hellman Key Exchange Algiorithm&lt;/b&gt; - Pinning is the process of associating a host with their expected X509 certificate or public key. Whitfield Diffie and Martin Hellman later went on to win the coveted &lt;b&gt;Turin award&lt;/b&gt; in 2015!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Material Design principles&lt;/b&gt; were introduced.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The store front of our app - The Restaurant Page - was made from scratch to include the product changes from UrbanSpoon.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The new look Home page with Material Design elements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v7/material_home.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pages with Material Design inspired cards&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v7/material_cards.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v7</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v7</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v6</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After winning the markets in India and the UAE, we started expanding to more geographies. This led to an acquisition of the market leaders in Poland, Czech Republic, Slovakia, Italy and New Zealand. We welcomed the challenge of introducing Zomato’s rich array of features with localized content while maintaining the familiarity of the old products - all this with one single apk file!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version also included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; Shift in Android Development Paradigm&lt;/b&gt; - After running into the 65k method reference limit, moving from Eclipse to Android Studio, switching to a MultiDex application, getting rid of Google Play Services binary to be replaced by individual jars, obfuscating the code-base using Proguard - we ended up changing a lot of the code-base during this time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Product Overhaul &amp;amp; New Geographies&lt;/b&gt; - Consolidation of regional leaders in new geographies meant that we had to evolve the product to ease the newly acquired users into our product. We integrated Text Menus, Daily Menus in our product. The new acquisitions included;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Obedovat in Slovakia&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Gastronauci In Poland&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cibando in Italy&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;MenuMania in New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Launched two new verticals of business&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Online Ordering&lt;/b&gt; - As displayed in the screen-shots at the bottom of this page, users could now place orders from their apps; we streamlined and automated a lot of this process of food take-outs and pickups.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cashless Transactions&lt;/b&gt; - This feature let the users to automate their payments through the Zomato app every time they went out to dine.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Searching for restaurants in Map view&lt;/b&gt; - Google Maps v2 APIs allowed us to plot restaurants on the map. Users could draw custom polygons on the map overlay and the restaurants in the area enclosed would be displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Android Wear Support&lt;/b&gt; - Keeping up with the latest trends, we integrated Zomato notifications with Android Wear.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Home page differs according to the Locale and Location of the user&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v6/home_locales.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;1000&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Screens demonstrating Online Ordering flow (Image 1 of 2)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v6/order_flow_1.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Screens demonstrating Online Ordering flow (Image 2 of 2)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v6/order_flow_2.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v6</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v6</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v5</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Users started to create lots of content on Zomato - reviews, photos and ratings. We used this surge of information created by the people to be used in beautiful endless scrolls of food feed to be used by other users. In true crowd-sourced fashion, we created a food guide that went beyond ratings and menus. It captured the moods of the commoners as well as the connoisseurs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenting the Food Feed! &lt;/b&gt; - World’s first timeline of food updates from around you and your friends. This increased the traction and the average session length of the app.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Home page&lt;/b&gt; - We completely redesigned the Home Page with a simple tab on top, re-ordering features on the home page according to their usage, the change was inevitable as we launched multiple new features that needed more face time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Presenting Collections &lt;/b&gt; - We made a new feature where restaurants were classified as a group on the basis of a common USP, this feture went on to become the most loved feature. Collections differed n each city and later we let the users create their own collections. From London’s Fish &amp;amp; Chips places to India’s street food, collections are a big hit.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; New Feature | Speed-dial/Bookmarks&lt;/b&gt; - This new feature allowed the users to maintain a list of their frequently visited restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt; New Splash &amp;amp; Login flow&lt;/b&gt; - We reduced the app launch time, optimized the login screens to increase conversions into registered users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Home Page with simple tabs, highlighting the two most exciting features - Feed and Collections!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v5/home.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;splash with the new Login screens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v5/login.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Feature | Collections&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v5/collections.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The new Restaurant page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v5/rest.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v5</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v5</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We stepped up our efforts to make Zomato an immersive experience for users of both kind - consumers &amp;amp; creators. Our then five member mobile team won the “App of the year” award by NDTV, beating the likes of WhatsApp, TrueCaller and PayTm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version included the following-&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;First-use User Experience&lt;/b&gt; - With the increased number of features in the app, we made use of On-boarding screens and first runs to simplify UX.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;User uploaded images&lt;/b&gt; - Using Android’s Camera API and NDK’s power, we made our very own in-app image uploading process, image filters and gallery views. We wrote our own thread for displaying the images in a gallery view inside the app keeping the limitations of Async threads in check.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Home Page&lt;/b&gt; - In a very significant change from the previous version, we split our single home page into a new page with four different tabs.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;On-boarding screens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v3/tour.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;1000&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Screens showing the photo upload flow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v3/photo_upload.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Splash screen and the Home page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v3/home.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v3</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v3</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zomato Android App v2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Introducing the Social Food Network - Zomato’s existing app could only search and list restaurants around your location. We took it to the next level by introducing users, the ability to review and rate restaurants, follow other foodies and comment on their activity. This new social level transformed Zomato from a listings product to a Foodie Network!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt; Major changes in this version included the following- &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Building the app from scratch&lt;/b&gt; - The entire app was written from scratch to include the concept of registering users, interaction of users with other users and restaurants. Search listings now included the recommendations of the user’s network making it very relevant. Some of the things being done for the first time in this version included-
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;User Page with their network of foodies and lists of favorite restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Restaurant Page with Photos, Menus and detailed information.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Search listings with recommendations from one’s network&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;City wise Leader-boards for Users and Restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Ability to create content - Writing reviews, rating restaurants and uploading pictures.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Integration with other social networks&lt;/b&gt; - For any decent network effect to take place we integrated with Facebook, Google, Instagram and Twitter to help users quickly log in and find their foodie friends n Zomato.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt; Here are some screens from this version- &lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Home Page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v2/home.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Search page &amp;amp; Restaurant page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v2/search_res.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;User could review and rate restaurants&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v2/create_content.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;User &amp;amp; Restaurant Leader-boards&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v2/leaderboard.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Login screen&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/img/sc_v2/login.jpg&quot; height=&quot;1000&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/Zomato-Android-App-v2</guid>
        
        
        <category>Zomato</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
